A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller 3rd papers FA108
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Audiovisual materials, 4
  - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation, 1958 (Reel AV 1017)
    Compilation of news footage: reporting on US funding of agriculture projects in the Philippines, then coverage of first Ramon Magsaysay Foundation award, with President Garcias and JDR 3rd.
    Philippines; Agriculture -- Asia.; Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (John Davison), 1906-1978; Garcia, Carlos P. (Carlos Polestico), 1896-1971
  - The Today Show: Performing Arts in America, 1965 March 9 (Reel AV 1654)
    A study of the performing arts in America, supported by JDR 3rd. The study stresses that the arts should have the same public funding and accessibility as museums or libraries, and the importance of bringing professional standards and quality to community and school-level programs. Barbara Walters and Hugh Downs are the interviewers.
    III 14.4-14
  - United Nations Population Explosion, 1967 (Reel AV 1653)
    Film on ABC about family planning in New York City, with sound bites from JDR 3rd and various international public leaders. Relates to article written by JDR 3rd "The Greatest Challenge" in Reader's Digest (1966 October).
    III 14.4-13
  - Urban Gateways: Art Safaris (Reel AV 873)
    Film from theater group funded by the JDR 3rd Fund
    IV 3B 10.11 Fe 1